they say Society plays an important role
in our lives it shapes our culture and
makes us the individuals we are today
but when Society begins to stereotype us
is when life begins to get difficult
[Music]
it's okay for him he's a boy men don't
cry women
should not be out late
[Music]
ICICI Lombard presents all okay please a
celebration of our diversity equity and
inclusion
come witness the Journey of our
champions from ICICI Lombard who went
beyond the tide to break every barrier
and every stereotype
foreign
I got behind the wheel on Sly and
convinced my father's driver to teach me
driving and three days later I was in
perfect control today I am a national
level racer and I have won close to 32
events including many events where I
have been the fastest woman driver well
I'm asked which is the most hair raising
event of your life there are many
but I will quote one in extreme races in
meghalaya my car toppled at a hairpin
bent at a very very high speed and
crashed it caught fire and I was pulled
out but here I am in front of you it's
definitely not easy being a woman driver
in male dominated sport like Motorsports
racing in most of the off-roading events
I still find myself as the only female
driver among loads of male participants
but next time whenever you make any
judgment on a woman driver think of me
from the time I can remember I've always
been a foodie but I cook pretty rarely
maybe once or twice a month at the most
but lockdown Mayberry
I became the designated chef of the
house throughout the lockdown and trust
me I loved it
YouTube recipes
but now I began experimenting with
traditional recipes I specialize in all
kinds of Cuisine North Indian South
Indian Chinese Thai Italian French and
while I experiment I'm also a purist in
cooking I love to prepare everything
right from scratch from the Bosa batter
to the pizza base
now that we are back to working from
office I indulge in my passion mainly on
weekends but if you still think cooking
is only a woman's job all I can say is
you've got to change your thinking
[Music]
I started weight training just three
years back and before I knew it I was
drawn to weight lifting as a sport my
fitness coach is a professional Olympic
weightlifter he pushed me to participate
at a district level competition and
other say Meri Journey started
it overpowers all negative thoughts
waking up at 5am intense training for
three hours followed by a two-hour
commute to work is not everybody's cup
of tea
[Music]
but weightlifting has taught me how to
remain confident in the face of any
adversity
I am a proper Mumbai car from shivaji
Park kite flying is very popular here
seeing colorful kites in the sky was a
great sight and flying it seems to be
great fun but a problem only boys were
flying kite and at the most my brothers
allowed me to hold the chakri and had
all the fun my name is why should boys
have all the fun and I resorted to
typical Bombay ajugar I started waking
up early much earlier than my brothers
and started training myself to fly a
kite
I think it was little tough I didn't
know how to select the right diet how to
tie a Kani but
in the morning one day after four or
five attempts my kite flew high and
thereafter no looking back it was so
liberating it was thrilling
[Music]
I have been a classical dancer since I
was 13.
Indian classical dance requires you to
be in a touch with your feminine as well
as a masculine side above Imaging
[Music]
side effects at first my friends used to
make fun of me but I got used to it at
Issa Lombard I feel out of home
in fact in talent show organized for our
founders day I was selected to do my
classical dance and got another chance
to pursue my passion
thank you
my Fascination for riding started early
college me I used to see the boys riding
this heavy fancy bikes and I always
thought why not me
biking is difficult for women bike
ladies but I just wanted to challenge
these thoughts
[Music]
I bought my first bike in 2006 since
then I have written to ladakh Srinagar
Manali spiti and many other circuits on
my way back from one of my Manali rides
recently I was badly stuck in a
landslide in spite of knowing that I
won't be able to join work the next day
my supervisor was worried about my
safety he assured me that he will manage
my work till I am back either office May
everyone respects my passion and lets me
be me
foreign
that's why I chose mixed martial art and
kickboxing
I am a national level kickboxer State
and District level gold medalist you may
not believe it but I can fight men and
women of any age group
women are not weak
every woman should be called a supreme
[Music]
at icic at Lombard we don't stereotype
anyone
we don't label anyone we don't restrict
because at ICICI Lombard we believe that
you do your best only when you are the
best version of yourself
[Music]